[theme music]
[siren blaring]
EMERGENCY
[wind gusting]
[phone ringing]
Hello. This is Team Two.
Yes. Why?
What? An accident?
[tense music]
"Accident"? What accident?
- [Dong-han] Did someone get hurt?
- [Soo-jin gasps]
[siren blaring]
[paramedic] Turn it around.
Hurry, hurry.
Doctor! Doctor!
- [nurse] It's critical.
- [moans in pain]
Healthy, late 20s, male.
[paramedic] Injured in an explosive blast,
unable to open his eyes.
100 over 60, 120bpm.
- Treatment room. Go now.
- Yes, sir.
- Does this patient have a guardian?
- [Yu-jin] I'm here.
I'm here for him.
Can I get his family and first name?
- [paper rustles]
- Lee Si-woo. He's with the KMA.
[worried mumbling]
[Dong-han] Who's hurt?
It's Mr. Lee.
[tense music]
The hospital says he's very hurt.
[Ha-kyung] You should go, Forecaster Lee.
[Si-woo sighs]
I have to go where?
The Jeju Typhoon Center.
You're a good fit.
Are you kidding me?
All the decisions I make at work
are taken seriously.
So that means
you've given this considerable thought.
Mm-hmm. If you're okay with it.
[Si-woo] If the body temperature drops
about one degree,
its level of immunity
becomes 30 percent weaker.
Ha-kyung doesn't date just anybody
unless there's a chance of marriage.
You are aware of that, right?
[Si-woo] That means it becomes that much
more vulnerable to external threats.
What are you…
What's this about?
We both need space.
I think it's important for both of us.
Yu-jin.
We should take some time to think
how we can make this work.
[sighs]
You know you need it as much as I do.
We do have some time still,
so you can let me know.
[inhales]
Uh, no.
I'll do it.
You should give it more thought.
There's nothing to go over now.
Like you said, it's official business.
[inhales]
I'll go.
[gentle music]
It's settled.
Anything you want to say?
Oh, no.
Okay.
[Si-woo] The same goes
for the temperature between two people.
If you leave me right now,
then that's it for us.
Have you thought carefully about this?
[sighs]
If that's what you want…
well, okay.
[door closes]
[luggage rattling]
[woman on PA system]
The 77-4 bus will be arriving shortly.
[brakes squeal]
[bus door opens]
[bus door squeaking]
[Si-woo] One tiny thing
someone says to you,
one small twitch of their face
can sometimes turn your emotions ice-cold.
And…
[Soo-jin] Oh, no.
There was an accident?
Where? Where and how bad was it?
Ho… hold on a moment. Who is this?
If you tell me
which hospital it is, I'll--
- [Yu-jin] This is Chae Yu-jin.
- [gasps]
[moans]
I'm with Si-woo right now.
[Si-woo] When your emotional temperature
drops even one degree,
you become highly sensitive,
vulnerable to the outside environment.
[beeps]
EPISODE 11
2 DAYS AGO
[bright music]
[upbeat music]
[squeaks]
[reporter on TV] Watch out for signs
of physical and mental exhaustion
as the hot weather continues.
Heat wave advisories have been issued
in the Yeongnam area
- and most of the western region.
- [sighs]
And the heat wave warning
has been issued in Gwangju.
INNOVATIVE WEATHER SERVICES
A STEPPING STONE TO PUBLIC SAFETY
Ah, hell. No sign of rain yet, Director?
There will be a light rain under 5mm
from the wind on the east coast.
However, it will only reach Gangwon.
That doesn't even count as rain, really.
[sighs]
Wow, red across the board.
The Ministry of the Interior and Safety
is going on the news
to announce some safety measures today.
Local governments have agreed
to try and set up heat shelter facilities.
- Okay.
- [Dong-han sighs]
A lot of government offices
are gonna get hit hard, huh?
- [Bong-chan] It's inevitable.
- [phone vibrates]
[Si-woo] What shall we do this weekend?
It's the last one before I leave for Jeju.
What are you doing?
[whispers]
What's wrong?
What? Go ahead.
Uh, yes, sir.
Let's start with impact forecast
for each region affected.
[phone vibrates]
[Si-woo] How about
duck baeksuk in Gapyeong?
Duck baeksuk in Gapyeong--
Hmm?
[comical music]
I apologize.
Uh, I think that an emphasis
on water temperature control
and shading near fish farms
would be appropriate.
Oh, and let's remind the press
to restrain from their catastrophizing.
We'll do our best, Director.
Thanks.
If there's nothing further,
we'll adjourn this meeting.
- Good work, all.
- Great work.
- Great job.
- [all] Thank you.
[man] Duck baeksuk in Gapyeong
sounds pretty good.
[Bong-chan] Oh, right.
Did you make your decision?
- The typhoon center, who's going?
- Uh, yes.
- It's typhoon season already?
- Yeah, someone's gotta go.
Well, who is it, huh?
You don't think it could be me, do you?
[Myung-ju sighs]
What? You haven't decided yet?
I'm going, sir. It's me.
Huh? It's you? Since when?
Yesterday.
[chuckles]
- Oh!
- Congratulations.
- [Soo-jin] Congrats.
- [Bong-chan] Okay, then.
Forecaster Lee and Director Jin,
I'll see you in my office.
Yes, sir.
[phone vibrates]
Oh, Bo-mi. Hey.
[Dong-han] Oh, okay.
I wish I could go to Jeju.
[Ha-kyung] You seem
so excited to go to Jeju.
[Si-woo] I'm not excited about Jeju.
I'm excited about the typhoon center.
I've always wanted to work there.
You know me. I love field work.
You told me that Headquarters
was your dream.
Now you're saying you prefer the field?
What can I say? I'm multi-talented.
Good for you and, uh, best of luck.
What's wrong?
You're the one that told me to go.
Anyway, I don't like
the duck baeksuk in Gapyeong idea.
[sighs]
[keyboards clacking]
We will now begin the briefing
for the 29th of July.
Currently in Korea, the lower atmosphere
is filled with hot and humid air,
and the upper atmosphere
is filled with hot and dry air.
The cause of this heat wave
is the North Pacific anticyclone
which has expanded to the south
and also the Tibetan anticyclone
from inland China heading westward.
ELECTRONIC CIVIL SERVICE CENTER
DIVORCE
[mouse clicks]
PETITION FOR DIVORCE
[pensive music]
[chuckling]
- Boo!
- [gasps]
What are you doing?
[laughs]
I thought I wouldn't see you here.
I told you my school trip
has one more day here.
So when's it done?
The last part's the weather chart
listing in ten minutes.
So we could have, uh, a bite soon, yeah?
The food at the cafeteria here
is really good.
Hmm…
Well, okay.
[chuckles]
What time should I be there?
Ah, you just call me, okay?
After class, yeah?
Okay.
Tomorrow?
[Bong-chan] Mm-hmm.
- Why? Should he not?
- It's too soon, sir.
I thought we'd have the whole week.
[Bong-chan] You know Director Sung
at the typhoon center. She's impatient.
All week, she's been bugging me
about when we're gonna send her
our forecaster.
She says they should come ASAP
to get acquainted
with the station practices,
to avoid any mistakes
when the typhoons really start.
What could I say?
I get her concerns.
But we have our own problems here.
You know it's crazy
because of the heat wave right now.
Couldn't he continue covering
all of that from down there? Huh?
- Uh…
- And aside from the heat,
I only told him
he's going to Jeju yesterday.
- [Ha-kyung] He needs time to prepare.
- No, it's fine.
He says it's fine, see?
Yeah. Of course, I can cover
the heat wave from Jeju.
It's really not a problem.
[Bong-chan] Okay! Great, then.
If that's really all,
he'll go this weekend.
All right. Dismissed.
[clears throat]
[Bong-chan sighs]
Jeez.
[door opens]
- [door closes]
- You can't just say yes so impulsively.
How are you gonna leave tomorrow?
You're not ready to go.
You didn't even want to go to Gapyeong
for duck baeksuk.
I don't have any weekend plans,
so I might as well go
to the typhoon center and work.
Are you serious or just making a scene?
Mm, half and half.
Regardless. We can talk to him again.
[Si-woo] Why are you flip-flopping?
This is also confusing now.
What do you mean?
Didn't you want some time for yourself,
away from me?
Isn't that why you wanted me
to go to Jeju?
Then how come you're mad
that I would leave a few days earlier?
[pensive music]
I think you're mistaken about something.
I don't ever let my own feelings get
in the way of official weather business.
Even in other relationships,
not once did I do that.
[breathes deeply]
There's no need for us
to talk to the General Director.
I'll just head out tomorrow, Director.
[pensive music]
- Reporter Cho.
- Yes?
Is Reporter Chae not here
for the briefing?
Uh… Oh, uh, I heard she took time off.
You haven't heard?
[gasps]
Ah! So that was today.
Yes.
- [both chuckling]
- I, uh, forgot when she was… Yeah.
- Right. Goodbye. See you.
- Okay, see you.
[gentle music]
WEATHER
[phone vibrates]
KI-JUN
[phone clacks]
[phone vibrates]
[Ki-jun] You took time off?
Seriously? Where are you right now?
Come back home. We need to talk in person.
[deep sigh]
FLIGHT RESERVATION
FROM SEOUL TO JEJU ISLAND
BOOK A FLIGHT
[breathes deeply]
[Ki-jun] Yu-jin.
[sighs]
[phone vibrates]
[Myung-ju] What's up?
The vibe is off here.
[Soo-jin] I think something went down
between the Director and Forecaster Lee
about the typhoon center.
You should do something, Mrs. Oh.
- I should?
- Huh?
[quirky music]
You have something to say, Ms. Oh?
Uh, do I?
Uh, it's…
[light chuckle]
[Myung-ju] Director…
So should we go for dinner later?
[playful music]
Wait, dinner?
Uh, well…
[chuckles]
Forecaster Lee is going to Jeju,
and of course he'll come back soon
since it's just a temporary dispatch.
But still, it would be nice
to have dinner together
and wish him luck before he leaves.
What do you say?
Sounds great.
Oh.
[chuckles]
Yeah, sure. Sounds great.
[awkward chuckle]
Mr. Shin, what do you say?
- I already have plans.
- [Myung-ju] Ah.
Could you reschedule?
It's the first Team Two dinner altogether.
Oh, that's true, though.
It'd be the first time.
[Soo-jin] We've never done that before
with this crew.
Well, it'd be great if you rescheduled,
Mr. Shin, to be with our team.
I really shouldn't. It's important.
[Seok-ho] I'm sorry.
Oh, well, I suppose it is what it is.
Let's do it.
Huh?
We should have a dinner
whoever can make it.
What do you say, Forecaster?
Yeah.
Well, okay, then.
I'll, uh, get us a reservation.
[chuckles anxiously]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[door closes]
What's wrong?
This entire dinner thing is just for you.
Why are you upset right now?
"Right now"?
I've never said I'm upset before,
so why would you say "right now"?
I've never once told you I'm upset
since the moment you said
I should go to Jeju.
- What's wrong with you, kid?
- [Si-woo] I'm not a kid.
I'm a man.
And in fact, I'm yours.
[water boiling]
[clicks]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey. Enjoy your lunch.
- Oh, hello.
- Hey.
- Who is this?
- My daughter.
- Oh, your daughter? Go ahead. Here.
- Please go ahead. Go.
- Sure, thanks.
- Adorable.
She's here for her school.
[server] Oh, she's so pretty.
- Right? Yup, she is.
- Uh-huh.
[chuckling]
Ah! Here at the, uh, KMA,
the forecasters have the most work,
so, uh, the… the others all know that,
so most of the time,
they'll let us eat first at lunch.
- Thank you. Oh, that's great.
- [server] Here.
Have some vegetables.
Oh, they got sausage.
[Dong-han] When I was a kid,
I had this all the time.
It's really good.
[chuckles]
[light upbeat music]
Mm, yeah. Mm.
Can we join you for lunch?
- Yeah, sure. Here.
- Oh, of course.
- [Soo-jin] Slide in right here.
- Oh, thanks.
This is my daughter, Um Bo-mi.
Ah, Um Bo-mi, huh?
- [Soo-jin] Hello.
- [Myung-ju] Hello.
These are some of the people
who work with me on the team.
Hello.
- Aw.
- Hello.
- She's beautiful.
- Right?
I guess she takes after her mom.
What are you saying?
Hey, I can see some
of her Papa's features there too.
Can you tell me
what brings you here, Bo-mi?
- Your Papa, huh?
- No, she's here for her school.
- [Soo-jin] Oh, a field trip.
- Mm. So, uh, do you like science?
Yes, I do.
- [Myung-ju chuckles]
- How did you know?
I heard students who come to our office
are looking for experience in fields
they like for their school records.
- I see.
- [Soo-jin] Oh.
[Myung-ju] You not only resemble your dad,
I'd say you've got
a science mind too, huh?
- Oh?
- You don't know?
Your Pa's the best meteorologist in Korea.
Oh, come on. That's not true.
- [all laughing]
- [Myung-ju] You are the best.
Bo-mi, here, try. Try this.
[Soo-jin] Aw, look at Mr. Um.
I didn't know you had a soft side.
You're a real tiger in the situation room.
- [Myung-ju chuckles]
- You're a lucky girl.
Mr. Um, sir.
Could I have a piece
of your sausage as well?
- What's this?
- [Soo-jin] Hmm?
[chuckles]
Can I?
You can perfectly well
get your own sausage.
Yup.
- [chuckling]
- Bo-mi, try.
Go on.
[uneasy music]
- It's good, right?
- [Myung-ju] You like it?
[shy chuckle]
[phone vibrates]
Mm.
Just a moment. Sorry.
- Okay.
- [Dong-han] Mm-hmm.
Eommoni.
[Myung-ju's mom-in-law] You need
to pick up the kids a little early today.
Huh?
Maybe it's because of the hot weather.
And my eyes hurt.
And I'm not feeling so great.
Ah. Well, I'm sorry.
We have a dinner with our, uh, department.
[Myung-ju] One of the forecasters
is going to Jeju.
The director herself arranged it,
so it'd be really hard for me
to not be there.
Uh, could my husband
just take the kids from you?
He's studying now. You know that.
[sighs]
Then I'll be right over
as soon as I am all through eating.
Okay. Yeah.
[sighs]
What to do?
I suggested it.
I can't back out of it now.
[sighs]
[pensive music]
[Si-woo] I'm not a kid.
I'm a man.
And in fact, I'm yours.
Hey, we're at work.
Then maybe you should say "Forecaster."
I know you want to…
to draw some kind of boundary
between professional and personal with us.
I understand how you feel,
and I'll do what I can
to cooperate like I said.
Still…
I'm Si-woo.
Not Han Ki-jun who you dated before.
It's Si-woo.
And none of this right now
is about that man.
I know what you went through with him,
how hurt you were.
I know why you're so scared
of office romance,
and why you're worried
about everyone finding out, okay?
Still, that was that relationship.
And this one is ours now.
I don't want you
comparing us all the time.
It doesn't feel good.
When did I ever compare you to Ki-jun?
The reason that you
kept me a secret at a distance,
treating me like a kid is all because
of what happened with Ki-jun, okay?
You're afraid you might see him in me
and maybe get hurt in the same way.
And get humiliated again…
just like you did before.
- Lee Si-woo…
- [Si-woo] It's true.
I can't consider getting married.
That's just not the way I'm built.
But still, I still want
to be in love with you.
I really…
really adore you.
And…
if that's confusing at all, I'm sorry.
I'm asking for just your love…
when there's nothing in the world
that I could bring to this.
And so…
I would understand
if you want to reconsider us.
You can.
But I can't do this casual.
I can't have some moderate tepid thing
where we draw lines for each other.
I really don't think I could.
What are you saying right now?
That you can…
While I'm in Jeju, think about it.
If you want to continue…
or break it off.
["The Day You Were Falling"
by John Park playing]
[door closes]
[phone vibrates]
FATHER
- [phone vibrates]
- [sighs]
[vibrating continues]
[phone vibrates]
Yes, Jin Ha-kyung.
I'll look into that
and follow it up. Thank you.
Okay.
KMA HEAT WAVE FORECAST
[eerie music]
THE WORST HEAT WAVE EVER!
THERE'S NO END TO IT
PEOPLE ARE GROWING TIRED
OF THE MURDEROUS HEAT
[sighs]
My god! This is ridiculous.
[Soo-jin] A treat.
Thanks to lovely Bo-mi. Thank you.
[chuckles]
[can opening]
Oh, Bo-mi's not here?
- In the restroom.
- [Myung-ju] Oh.
- Go ahead. Get a drink.
- On you?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'll get that one, then.
[coins clinking]
- Is it good?
- [Soo-jin] Mm-hmm.
[coughing]
- [water running]
- [gasps, coughs]
[ominous music]
[coughs]
[labored breathing]
PETITION FOR DIVORCE
[gloomy music]
[printer whirring]
[sighs]
[mouse clicking]
[water running]
- [choking]
- [door opens]
- [thuds]
- Oh, gosh!
Honey! Honey, are you okay?
Appa. My father, please.
Oh, my god.
- [Soo-jin] She's lucky.
- It is luck.
- Oh, I'm fair pretty too.
- [Soo-jin] If I just got her skin…
[Si-woo] Did you have lunch?
- Yeah.
- Oh, Forecaster.
[woman] Hey! Someone, please help!
A student collapsed over here!
A student's in there,
on the floor in the bathroom,
- and she's choking.
- Um Bo-mi.
- [gasps]
- [Myung-ju] Oh, my!
- Hey! Call 119! 119! Hurry!
- Okay.
[tense music]
[siren wailing]
EMERGENCY CENTER
- [Dong-han] Hey.
- What's going on? Where is she?
[sighs]
I don't know what…
She was fine when we were having lunch,
but she collapsed
in the bathroom right after.
She couldn't breathe
and had a terrible sort of rash
- on her whole neck that went down.
- And what did you feed her?
She ate at the cafeteria.
What was the food there, though?
Uh, there was rice, seaweed,
and radish, pork sausage, and soup.
You gave pork to our daughter?
Yeah.
Bo-mi has always been allergic to that.
Did you forget?
Bo-mi, here. Try this.
[uneasy music]
- It's good, right?
- [Myung-ju] You like it?
I can't believe you.
[gloomy music]
[sighs]
"The worst heat yet! No end in sight.
Murder by heat in Korea."
I told you not to let them
get so sensational.
Han Ki-jun, listen!
Yu-jin has left.
What?
She wants to live alone.
Why?
What am I supposed to do now, Ha-kyung?
[slurps]
[somber music]
[line dials, rings]
[door closes]
Hey, Mom.
How are you? Everything good?
No, I just miss you,
and I wanted to hear your voice.
Yeah, he's doing well, of course.
[Ki-jun] She doesn't pick up the phone.
And she doesn't read my texts.
How did this happen?
Is it 'cause of her living with her ex?
[sighs deeply]
Uh, or did something else go down?
Hey.
Did you know that when we dated,
I felt like your work was a whole lot
more important than me, you know?
Every time I felt that way, I got sad
because I felt like
I would always be your second.
At the same time, I couldn't help
but feel like I was small and juvenile
for having all of those thoughts.
I did that to you?
Mm-hmm.
You did.
You're very authoritative when you say
you need to focus on your work life.
Of course, you said that to me
as a deputy director.
Still, I was your boyfriend first.
I felt awful so many times 'cause of that.
I know you want to draw a boundary
between professional and personal with us.
I understand how you feel,
and I'll do what I can
to cooperate like I said.
Still…
But…
[Ki-jun sighs]
[exhales sharply]
One day, I realized that
I was doing the same thing to Yu-jin.
I was comparing her to you
over every little thing.
[Si-woo] That was that relationship.
And this one is ours now.
I don't want you comparing us
all the time.
It doesn't feel good.
Yu-jin is just Yu-jin.
[Si-woo] I'm Si-woo.
Not Han Ki-jun who you dated before.
It's Si-woo.
[Si-woo] And none of this right now
is about that man.
[sighs]
[pensive music]
[Myung-ju] Don't worry.
I took care of everything.
Yeah. Ah, you're here.
Mr. Um's daughter is okay.
It looks like she made it through
the worst of it. She'll be all right.
That's good.
Uh, about our team dinner--
Forecaster Lee is gonna meet us
straight at the restaurant.
And Mr. Um will join us if the situation
with his daughter improves enough.
[sighs]
Right.
[relieved sigh]
[pensive music]
Here. Have this.
Oh, thank you.
Studying was the easiest thing
for me to do.
I knew what I had to do
to get good grades.
[breathes deeply]
But this damn weather and family, though,
I have no idea
how to wrap my head around it.
There's no equation, manual.
I never learned how to be a good father.
I don't have the smallest idea…
how to be a good husband or dad.
The fact that you worry about all that…
means you are one already.
You know,
I've never once seen my dad
think about any of that stuff.
Just putting that out there.
[chuckles]
How's Bo-mi?
She's better now.
[Hyang-rae] She'll have
to be discharged late tonight
when the sedative they had
to give her has worn off.
You should get going.
I thought her dermatitis had improved.
[Hyang-rae sighs]
How many diseases in the world
just go away on their own?
She stays well because of
the protection I provide her.
What she eats, where she sleeps,
the clothes she wears.
I'm sorry.
For what?
'Cause I almost killed her,
pretending to be a good dad
and knowing nothing.
[scoffs]
How could you know…
enough to be able to even pretend?
[doors opens]
[sighs]
[phone vibrates]
[crickets chirping]
- Are you going out?
- Huh?
Yeah. I have a research interview.
Where are you going?
Where do you have to go at night?
You're not going to Ha-kyung's again.
You think Ha-kyung's
the only thing important in my life?
Well, sort of.
Don't be late.
And don't drink too much either.
[huffs]
MOTHER-IN-LAW
[phone vibrates]
- [Soo-jin] Are you sure you're okay?
- Hmm? Why?
Your mother-in-law called.
She's been calling for a while now.
[chuckles]
If it's really so bad,
then she can call her own son.
You know he's studying.
Yes. And here I am
working to support him too.
From time to time,
I need a little chance to breathe.
I'm going to enjoy the food tonight.
I'll eat and drink and noraebang later?
[chuckles]
Oh, uh, Mr. Shin. So what's he up to?
Normally, he works and goes home.
A new girlfriend?
Ah, you know, he should
be dating at his age.
Mm.
- [Myung-ju] Director. Over here.
- Here.
Oh.
[chuckles]
[playful music]
I can see that you've worked very hard
on these drawings.
[sighs]
It's good for nothing.
I don't even know
where I should go with all of it.
Why did you choose the penguin?
They're cute. Why not?
In what way are they cute?
Hmm…
Well, I think about the way they walk,
it's adorable.
Waddle, waddle.
[chuckles]
[groans]
They, um, don't walk
that way to look cute.
Sorry?
Um, penguins waddle
'cause their ambulation is…
They follow a pendulum system.
If a pendulum reaches
its peak on one side,
it pauses for a moment for the energy
to change from potential back to kinetic.
Uh… Yeah.
Oh…
I had no idea. Okay. So?
Uh…
So?
- Uh…
- [pages rustle]
- When the penguin waddles like that…
- Uh-huh.
…it can save up to 80 percent
of the energy it needs.
Mm, save energy.
So, uh, the really cool thing
about them is this real efficiency.
- Oh, really? Hmm.
- [chuckles]
[mumbling]
Eighty percent…
[Seok-ho giggles]
Uh, also…
the penguins' blood vessels
are wrapped in a very unique pattern.
The "wonder net."
The veins and arteries
are all intertwined, so…
Whoa, you really know a lot.
[giggles]
You are a zoologist!
[Seok-ho] No, no.
Everyone's taking their time, huh?
Yeah, they all said
they would run a little late.
Maybe we should order something first?
Here, Director. We're all hungry.
- Oh, no. You, Ms. Oh.
- Ah, um, what should we order?
[Soo-jin] Let's start
with some pork belly. Yeah.
[Myung-ju] Hmm, that okay, Director?
[gentle music]
- [bell chimes]
- [sighs]
Ooh.
Go ahead. You young people
love this kind of thing.
Oh, okay.
Uh, why did you want
to meet all of a sudden?
[sighs]
Let's eat first, and then we'll talk.
- Uh…
- [utensils clanking]
Ooh.
[Mrs. Bae giggles]
[Mrs. Bae] Uh…
How's Ha-kyung doing now?
She's swamped with work
because of the heat wave.
She hasn't said anything
since my last visit with her, though?
No. Not really. No.
I was so off guard.
She threw the not-getting-married thing
at me,
and I was mortified, I had to back off,
and let it all just go.
Ah, you know, the one who lives upstairs--
Not Seok-ho, not that man.
Why?
He's not right for the Director.
Their personalities, tastes,
hobbies, lifestyles,
nothing in common at all.
I can say that for sure.
Ah, but they can find those things
when they're together.
To put it bluntly,
they're two different people,
two different lives, two sets of parents.
I mean, how can everything
be perfect from the beginning?
It would be weird
if there were no differences.
You… have a point.
You see, marriage isn't about
a couple perfectly coming together.
The joining comes first,
so they can perfect each other, huh?
This process is what married life is for,
so at the end of that is a good couple.
Young people these days think
that it's some kind of insurance plan
or just some sort of big legal headache.
That's why most won't even give it a try.
They're busy calculating
all the conditions and the concerns.
You've never regretted yours, then?
What?
Your own marriage, you know?
[breathes deeply]
Well, uh…
I've always regretted it.
I've said that he's my worst enemy
and I hope lightning kills him.
But…
if someone asks me if I would do it again,
if I could somehow go back in time,
well, I'd probably say yes.
Why?
[chuckles]
Through it all, we had
some pretty good times, him and I, too.
Especially with Tae-kyung and Ha-kyung.
And those girls are the finest works
I've ever created.
[chuckles]
- So what I want to say to you is--
- But still, I really mean it.
Not Seok-ho. Not with Ha-kyung.
Not ever.
Why are you being so obstinate?
Who are you to say?
[light music]
Oh, the pizza is getting cold, ma'am.
[awkward chuckle]
Please. I'll grab you a slice.
Mm.
[sighs]
Looks like our dinner's not working out.
What do you mean?
[Myung-ju] We're having it right now.
Quite deliciously, I might add.
Mrs. Oh, looks like you forgot
why you called for this event.
First, it's to say goodbye
to Forecaster Lee.
Second, it's supposed to be
the first ever get-together
of our current team, isn't it?
Well, what can we do now?
They're not gonna show up.
It's their loss if they're not here.
Even though the Director herself
put it together.
[Myung-ju] We can't control them.
Everything is what it is.
So let's get two more orders.
We'll rename this night
as a well-deserved retreat
just for the women of Team Two.
Do you approve, Director?
What do you say?
Okay.
- A women's retreat sounds great.
- [giggles]
Sir, could we please get
two more pork belly orders?
- Soju too.
- [man] You got it.
We're ordering some soju?
Well, now that we've re-christened
our night, we might as well.
- Ooh!
- How's that sound?
Mm, thanks.
[tapping]
Oh, wow. Oh, wow. Oh, wow.
[chuckling]
- Here you go.
- Oh, yes. All right.
- Noraebang later?
- Well, of course!
- Of course.
- Yay!
- Cheers.
- [Soo-jin] Cheers.
[Myung-ju] Cheers.
- [Myung-ju] Let's go. Let's go.
- [Soo-jin] Let's go. This place!
[laughter]
Do we have to go in here?
I have to go home.
- Hey! Why are you going home?
- Let's barbecue now!
- You are such a good singer.
- Come on. Just one more.
- [laughter]
- I'm a high soprano.
- High soprano.
- I don't think their songs in low keys
are real songs.
- [Myung-ju] I'm a baritone.
- [all laughing]
[laughter]
[line ringing]
DIRECTOR JIN HA-KYUNG
[beeps]
[sighs]
[gentle music]
[phone vibrates]
Yes, Ms. Oh.
Where are you right now?
[Myung-ju] The Director is so drunk.
I have to go home now.
I'm sorry but can you come
pick her up, Forecaster Lee?
[sighs]
[Si-woo] I'm here.
How drunk are you?
Can you walk on your own?
I want things to work out.
I want things to work out
for the two of us.
But…
that's the only thing.
A love that stays under control
with tempered feelings.
I like it simple and stable.
If things start to go beyond moderate…
I become anxious.
Then I feel…
I become someone else and not myself.
[gentle music]
So all I can do…
is do it moderately.
Get up. Let's take you back home.
So then you should decide.
You should decide while you're in Jeju.
If you think you can do it
moderately or not.
Really think about it then decide.
[Si-woo] One of my superiors once told me…
that when I don't understand
a satellite image,
no matter how long I've looked at it,
I should stand a little further away
and observe the flow of the clouds."
[emotional music]
To be honest, I didn't understand
what he said at the time.
I've never seen a satellite image
I didn't understand back then,
and I was very confident
about everything related to weather.
Then…
I met you.
[emotional music fades]
[gasps]
Oh, my head.
[groans]
[breathes deeply]
[Ha-kyung] Oh.
[chuckles]
[groans]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Oh, you're flying right after work?
That's my stuff.
Oh, you scared me.
[sighs]
- [door closes]
- Uh, are you moving home?
No. I was thinking I would stay
at the office again
since it's typhoon season, you know.
Where is Lee Si-woo?
Si-woo left.
Sorry?
Jeju. He left today. You didn't know?
Anyway, soup over there
to nurse your head.
[wistful music]
[plane zooming]
[Si-woo] Did you know
you were the strangest weather
I've ever seen in my life?
[sighs]
Uh…
[gasps]
There was an accident? Where?
Where and how bad is it?
[Ha-kyung] I…
Hold on a moment. Who is this?
If you tell me
which hospital it is, I'll--
[Yu-jin] This is Chae Yu-jin.
[sighs]
I'm with Si-woo right now.
[winces]
[pensive music]
[phone vibrates]
- [sighs]
- [phone vibrates]
Hello?
Why are you calling me so late?
Wait, what's that?
[Ki-jun panting]
Ha-kyung. What the hell's going on?
Lee Si-woo is hurt.
Okay, I get Lee Si-woo is hurt.
But why on earth
is he there right now with Yu-jin?
- Coincidence.
- What?
In Jeju, they ran into each other.
[sighs]
EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
[tense music]
Lee Si-woo.
[sighs]
This is all your fault.
How is this my fault?
I was so scared
of an office romance because of you,
that I was always on edge
with Si-woo and so afraid.
Uh, you were always on edge
and scared even when you were with me.
I was scared of you!
[sobs]
I was so consumed
by the fear of getting hurt.
Now that I never told him
how I really felt.
Or did anything.
Now what do I do?
What do I do?
[Ha-kyung sobbing]
What do I do now?
[Ha-kyung bawling]
[Ha-kyung] So it wasn't because
of Lee Si-woo's principle
of not wanting to get married.
I was scared that it would get too hot,
too hot to the point
where I can't control it.
I was afraid to lose control
of my emotions, so I was making excuses
to stop the last one degree from rising
to reach the boiling point.
But…
[Dong-han sighs]
- Mr. Um.
- [Dong-han] Hmm?
[foreboding music]
- Wow. When did that start, huh?
- Oh!
[phone ringing]
Hello. Headquarters. This is Um.
Yeah. We just saw it.
It is a…
[Sung] Typhoon, yes.
Number 15 Elisha
that was following Number 14 Ricky.
Around eleven o'clock today,
it was moving northeastward,
300km near Okinawa.
The central pressure was 990,
max wind velocity 20 per second,
and a radius of 150.
- [man] That's it.
- Can I have that?
[indistinct chatter]
NATIONAL TYPHOON CENTER
[man] Satellite Center. Can you check
the intensity of the typhoon?
At 10:00 p.m., we're looking at a path
straight for the southern Jeju Sea,
120km over the western sea near Okinawa.
980 central pressure,
max velocity, 28, strong wind, 200.
[Dong-han sighs]
Mm, I understand.
- Keep sending us the data. Mm-hmm.
- [phone clanks]
- Mr. Shin.
- [Seok-ho] Yes?
Give me data on ocean heat change
by time period.
- Yes, sir.
- [Dong-han] Ms. Oh.
Figure out steering current flow
and the vertical wind sheer
from the updated forecast.
[Myung-ju] Yes, sir.
VERTICAL WIND SHEAR:
CHANGE IN WINDSPEED WITH HEIGHT
STEERING FLOW: THE FLOW
THAT INFLUENCES TYPHOON MOVEMENT
[unsettling music]
[tense music]
[door handle clanks]
You're all dead, all of you.
[unsettling music]
[Ha-kyung sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
INNOVATIVE WEATHER SERVICES
A STEPPING STONE TO PUBLIC SAFETY
[suspenseful music]
[thunder roars]
["Open Your Heart" by Lyn playing]
[Ki-jun] I didn't realize
you were so invested.
Who knows what I feel?
It seems like everything's falling apart.
I want to talk to the guy in charge.
- I can't calm down!
- What's going on?
[Ki-jun] What you're doing
is obstructing official duties.
It's important
that they can do their work.
[Hyang-rae] No. No more. Just be
a decent man for once and sign it.
[Ki-jun] Except Yu-jin left me now, so…
Can you let me go?
Is there any way
I could come along to Jeju Island?
[Ha-kyung] There's so much that we expect
people we love to figure out.
But what if we took nothing for granted
- and said everything explicitly?
- Yu-jin.
[Si-woo] All I really wanted was time
to realign and be together.
I must have missed where we fell out.